<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personalised Celebrancy Manawatu Ltd. on Celebrancy for Life, Palmerston North, Manawatu, New Zealand</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personalised Celebrancy Manawatu Ltd. on Celebrancy for Life, Palmerston North, Manawatu, New Zealand</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 00:33:53 +1200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Birth Celebrancy</title>
      <link>/pages/birth-celebrant/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 00:33:53 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pages/birth-celebrant/</guid>
      <description>The miracle of a new baby! After 9 months of waiting he or she has arrived – your lives will never be the same again.
So enriching, so precious is your new bundle of potentiality that you want to celebrate with family &amp; friends – in ways like:
 Baby naming Baby blessing/christening/dedication Family &amp; home blessing First birthday party  Please contact me if you require Birth Celebrant services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Celebrancy Fees</title>
      <link>/pages/celebrant-fees/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 00:33:53 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pages/celebrant-fees/</guid>
      <description>Birth celebrant fees
Fee by negotiation, depending on your needs. Life celebrant fees
Fee by negotiation, depending on your needs. Marriage celebrant fees
The base fee for my marriage celebrancy is $350 (including GST). This fee could increase if you require additional services. Funeral celebrant fees
The base fee for my funeral celebrancy is $350 (including GST). This fee could increase if you require additional services.  Testimonials I can highly recommend Llew as a funeral celebrant for anyone who wants a service filled with dignity and that personal touch which helps make the day a memorable one for family and friends (read full testimonial).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Funeral Celebrancy</title>
      <link>/pages/funeral-celebrant/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 00:33:53 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pages/funeral-celebrant/</guid>
      <description>We humans are wired to be relational beings who are closely connected to family &amp; friends. When a loved-one passes away we feel the pain deep with-in us. At the time it feels unreal, even surreal – we need someone to give us the advice we need for all that is taking place &amp; needs to take place, for example :
 Pre-funeral advice Planning the funeral Conducting the funeral Post-funeral help Please contact me if you require Funeral Celebrant services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gridtest page</title>
      <link>/debug/gridtest/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 00:33:53 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/debug/gridtest/</guid>
      <description> Does this website work for you? Email problems, feedback, or other corrections to apologianz AT gmail DOT com   Latest Hugo releases here Latest Bootstrap releases here      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heads up</title>
      <link>/pages/heads-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 00:33:53 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pages/heads-up/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John and Holly’s Wedding</title>
      <link>/pages/photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 00:33:53 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pages/photos/</guid>
      <description>Llew officiating at John and Holly&#39;s wedding.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life Celebrancy</title>
      <link>/pages/life-celebrant/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 00:33:53 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pages/life-celebrant/</guid>
      <description>Life will always have its challenges – it doesn’t always go the way we have it planned. The unexpected comes along in its own unique way causing us to wonder what’s going on &amp; why. At times like this it’s very helpful to have someone to talk to, someone who will listen – someone who’s been through ‘stuff’ &amp; who understands the processes of life, in areas like:
 Employment challenges Family problems Addiction help Life-counsel Motivational coaching/speaking Immigration support  Please contact me if you require Life Celebrant services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marriage Celebrancy</title>
      <link>/pages/marriage-celebrant/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 00:33:53 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pages/marriage-celebrant/</guid>
      <description>A man &amp; a woman coming together to commit themselves to one another in a new love-adventure called Marriage.
The need for preparation, the special Wedding day – making it an unforgettable experience for you &amp; your family &amp; friends.
Helping you make it the very best this occasion can be, by assisting you with:
 Wedding planning Marriage preparation Wedding Service Post-marriage advice  Please contact me if you require Marriage Celebrant services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testimonials</title>
      <link>/pages/testimonials/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 00:33:53 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pages/testimonials/</guid>
      <description>Testimonial I can highly recommend Llew as a funeral celebrant for anyone who wants a service filled with dignity and that personal touch which helps make the day a memorable one for family and friends.
Llew is a helpful and compassionate person, He can facilitate a simple, no fuss service to a more contemporary celebration of a life with, or without, spiritual content. He is professional in his approach, being there at all stages of the planning, helping people to relax, guiding them through the service, incorporating the ideas and wishes of the family, and making suggestions from his years of experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Celebrancy for Life</title>
      <link>/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 21:52:41 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>Over the past 35 years, I have had the amazing privilege and honour of being involved with people at significant times in their lives. I have helped people celebrate and mourn in a way that is unique and meaningful and planned by their family. In doing so, I have developed the compassion needed to help people face the challenges of life and walk the journey. Llew pictured with Ann, his wife of over 43 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/pages/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 21:52:37 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pages/contact/</guid>
      <description>Please contact me if you wish to further discuss your requirements.
If your enquiry is urgent, please contact me on: 027 435 7009.
Alternatively, email me at : LLEW@celebrancyforlife.co.nz</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>